<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Poole</title>
 <link href="http://getpoole.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://getpoole.com/"/>
 <updated>2016-06-13T13:06:49-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://getpoole.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Mark Otto</name>
   <email>markdotto@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>In mobile, disruption comes from above</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2016/01/03/introduction/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-03T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2016/01/03/introduction</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;Most revolutionary new technologies follow a similar evolutionary path from utility to fashion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the automobile was first mass produced in the early 1900s, it was practically impossible to use and literally impossible for most people to purchase. It was horribly underpowered by any comparative standard except the horse. For the first thirty years or so, the car slowly improved in style, power, and comfort. Each new model was principally defined by its technological improvement–slightly better performance, more comfortable interior, or lower cost. By 1935, the car was more or less feature-complete. By then, the entire Oldsmobile line had electric starters, comfortable transmissions, and a well-sealed passenger cabin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde&lt;/em&gt; tells the story of a lawyer investigating the connection of two persons, Dr. Henry Jekyll and Mr. Edward Hyde. Chief among the novel’s supporting cast is a man by the name of Mr. Poole, Dr. Jekyll’s loyal butler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This kind of ‘reverse disruption’ also happens with other advanced, expensive hardware technology products like the automobile, the computer, the television, etc. But the bottom-up disruption pattern is way more common, and almost universally true for applications of those expensive products, especially apps, services, and the industries built on top of them.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Fixing Twitter</title>
   <link href="http://getpoole.com/2016/01/01/fixing-twitter/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-01T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://getpoole.com/2016/01/01/fixing-twitter</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tech analyst Startup L. Jackson believes that Twitter’s Product is Fucking Fine and that the company’s next CEO needs to simply give the current team some room to get stuff done. No. I think Twitter badly needs to do at least five things to address imminent existential threats–things which its current team has tried and spectacularly failed to accomplish. Investor/cowboy Chris Sacca recently wrote about What Twitter Can Be; below I outline what I think Twitter should have been yesterday–and how its team has proven an inability to address or even identify these threats over the past three years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, for normal users, Twitter feels too much like a one-way broadcast system. It needs to feel more like a community, with meaningful two-way interaction. Right now, a reply to Justin Bieber by a 16-year-old fangirl goes into the ether, never to be seen again. There is zero incentive in the product to interact with celebrities on Twitter, because no one will see the responses. Instagram at least gives the illusion that other people will see interactions, and its UI even feels like a realtime chat room. Twitter responses are difficult to read on the website–with that weird accordion expansion UI that only shows 5 responses and makes it impossible to follow a coherent conversation. It is insane that Twitter has not improved the reply/conversations system.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
